Contact

kyle.schnarrs@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kyle-schnarrs-82317a149 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Basic Life Support (BLS)
Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)
CPI Training

Certifications

IS-00700.a National Incident Management System (NIMS) An Introduction

IS-00907 Active Shooter: What Can You Do

Pre-Hospital Registered Nurse Registered Nurse

CCRN

Kyle Schnarrs

BSN, RN, CCRN-CMC, CEN, CFRN, PHRN Critical Care Transport Nurse

Cleveland/Akron, Ohio Area

Summary

BSN with Critical Care, Emergency, Critical Care Transport, and Pre Hospital experience. I am certified in multiple aspects of critical care and emergency medicine. I have a passion for nursing and strive daily to make myself a better nurse.

Experience

University Hospitals
1 year 6 months

Critical Care Transport Registered Nurse April 2020 - Present (3 months) Cleveland, Ohio, United States

Adult, pediatric, and neonatal critical care transport nurse via ambulance. Rotor wing flight transports when needed for neonates.

Registered Nurse Emergency Department January 2019 - April 2020 (1 year 4 months) Cleveland, Ohio

Level 1 Trauma Emergency Nurse

TRI-COUNTY AMBULANCE SERVICE, INC.
Mobile Intensive Care Unit Nurse
March 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months)
Mentor, Ohio

Critical Care Transport Nurse

Cleveland Clinic Hillcrest Hospital Registered Nurse Emergency Department September 2018 - December 2018 (4 months) Mayfield Heights, Ohio

Level 2 Trauma Emergency Department Nurse

University Hospitals

Cardiac ICU Clinical Nurse March 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 7 months) Cleveland, Ohio

EmergyCare MICU PHRN January 2018 - July 2018 (7 months) Erie, Pennsylvania

Mercy Health (Youngstown)
Patient Care Associate
October 2015 - December 2016 (1 year 3 months)
Warren, Ohio

Hot Head Burritos Crew Member March 2014 - October 2015 (1 year 8 months) Niles, Ohio

Vienna Short Holes Golf Course Grounds Keeper, Cashier, Lesson Assistant May 2007 - September 2014 (7 years 5 months) Vienna, Ohio

Giant Eagle, Inc.
Pharmacy Technician
September 2012 - May 2013 (9 months)
Middleburg Heights, Ohio

Education

Ohio University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2017 - 2018)

Kent State University at Ashtabula
Associate of Science - AS, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2013 - 2016)